(Sheldon:)You laugh now,
you just wait until you need tech support.
(Penny:)Gosh. He's kind of a sore loser, isn't he?
(Leonard:)Well, to be fair,
he's also a rather unpleasant winner.
(Penny:)Well, it's been fun.
(Leonard:)Penny, we make such a good team.
(Leonard:)Maybe we could enter
a couple of "Halo" tournaments sometime.
(Penny:)Or we could just have a life.
(Leonard:)I guess for you, that's an option.
Ha-ha. Ha.
- Good night, Leonard.
- Good night.
(Penny:)As usual, nice talking to you, Raj.
(Raj:)What do you suppose she meant by that?
(Leonard:)She's an enigma, Raj.
(Sheldon:)There's a certain ethic to the game,
Penny, a well-established...
(Leonard:)She's gone, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Well, she could have said goodbye.
(Penny(entering again):)Okay, I have a problem.
(Sheldon:)It's called carpal tunnel syndrome,
and quite frankly, you deserve it.
(Leonard:)What's wrong?
Well, um, Howard and Christy
are kind of hooking up in my bedroom.